ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4070
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files
1918-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Office of the Dean
/4070
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3111350
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 26, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4123: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Deans Office.
3111350
- P-1 -- Aaron, Benjamin, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports - Mimi Abramovitz, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Adams, Bristow, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- P-1 Adler, Joseph, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- P-1 -- Ahmad. Eqbal, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- P-1 Alers, J. Oscar, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annual Reports- David G. Alexander, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- P-1 Allen, Russell W., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- P-1 Allen, William H., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- P-1 -- Arons, Mark L., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- P-1 Aronson, Judith E., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- P-1 Asherman, Ira Gilbert, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Atteslander, Peter N., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- P-1 Bailey, Peggy, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- P-1 Banerjee, Dr. K.S., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Barton, Betty, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Beach, C. Kenneth, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Beal, Edwin F., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Beck, Mary, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- P-1 - Belasco, James, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- P-1 Bergen, Theodora, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Billmyer, David, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- P-1 Blanchard, John, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- P-1 Bloch, Herman, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bloch, Herman, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- P-1 Blough, Margaret, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Boorman, Paul H., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- P-1 Bradfield, Leila, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bradley, Phillips, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- P-1 Breer, Paul E., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Brittain, John A., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Broderick, Walter, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Brophy, John M., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Brownrigg, Wm., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- P-1 Brunetti, Pier, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- P-1 Budke, Harriet L., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- P-1 Burling, Temple, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- P-1 Carares, Ricardo H., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- P-1 Galvert, Bette, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- P-1 Campbell, James, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- P-1 -- Chapple, Eliot D., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- P-1 Cheek, Neil H., Jr., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cole, David L., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- P-1 Connors, William E., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Delliquadri, Carmen (Mr.), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- DeRose, Louis J., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Dierlam, Robert J., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Dorr, Mary L., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Douglas, Ann, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- P-1 Duino, Russell, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- P-1 Dwyer, Charles, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- P-1 Eckert, Leone, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Ellison, Sara, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Epstein, Ethel S., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- P-1 Erickson, Rodney, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Estey, Marten S., 1948-1952 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Evans, Hywel Wynn, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- P-1 Feldman, Janet C., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fernandez, Marta, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- P-1 Fetterman, Lawrence, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- P-1 Fields, Terry J., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Ford, Saville T., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Forsberg, Clarence, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Forsberg, Clarence, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Frank, Richard De Korn, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Fuller, Gretta, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Garbarino, J. W., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- P-1 -- Gellermann, Wmp, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- P-1 Goil, Ram H., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Goldberg, Davetta M. (Miss), 1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- P-1 Goldsen, Rose, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Golub, Fred T., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Goodman, Eleanor (Mrs. Corvini), 1954 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Gordon, Paul J., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Gordon, Richard, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Gow, Jean A. (Mrs.), 1952 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- P-1 Gregory, Peter, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Gulick, Charles A., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- P-1 Hagood, Kenneth D., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Hale, Merle C., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Hanna, Michael R., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Hardman, J. B. S., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Harris, Edwin F., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- P-1 Hawryluk, Alexander, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Hecht, Evelyn B. (Mrs.), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- P-1 -- Helms, Marie, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- P-1 Hepton, Estelle, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Hewitt, Cynthia N., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- P-1 Hill, James, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Hohensinn, Frans, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Hollister, Margaret, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- P-1 Holloway, Gordon, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Horowitz. Martin, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- P-1 Howard, Rhoda (Box 2, Folder 57)
- P-1 - Hsu, Ursula D., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Hudson, Archibald, E., 1952 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Huggler, Mardean, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Hyatt, David, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Irvin, Floyd - P-1, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Isaacson, William J., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Jackson, Joseph, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- James, Ralph Jr., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- P-1 Jeffrey, Newman, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Jochen, Albert E., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Johnson, James W., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Kaufman, Jacob J., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- P-1 Keenahan, Laura C., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- P-1 Kendall, Lorne Melvin, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Kent, Ronald W., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- P-1 Knickerbocker, Helaine J., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Knowles, Kenneth GuyJ, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- P-1 Kogan, Marvin, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- P-1 Komar, Judith, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Kouzian, Ardemis, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Kress, A. L., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- P-1 - Laaksonen, Oiva, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- P-1 -- Lamb, Robt. S. (Catalog Librarian) Sept. 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Lampert, Bernard, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Landis, Elizabeth, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- P-1 Landsberger, Henry A., 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Leibowitz, Walter L., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Lentz, Edith, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- P-12 Lindsey, Christopher, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- P-1 Lisberger, Theodore, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Little, John F., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- P-1 Locke, Edward, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Longaker, William D., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Marlow, H. LeRoy, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Marquadt, Mary, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Martin, Albert A., 1956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Martin, Philip C., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- P-1 -- Matthews, And, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Mayer, Jerome, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- McCaffree, Kenneth M., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- P-1 McCauley, John, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- McLean, Alan, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Mertens, Charles, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Montgomery, Royal, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Moody, Anne Mae P-1 File, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Morgenroth, George W., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Morrison, Nathan, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Morrison, Riley A., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Morton, Joseph E., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- P-1 Moyer, Helen, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Mullady, Philomena M., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- P-1 Nell, Antonia H., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Nelson, Ulia L., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Newkirk, Louis V., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- P-1 Newman, Harold R., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Nicander, Vivian, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- P-1 Noble, Nathaniel, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Ollie, Hazel O. (Mrs.), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- P-1 Olson, Nancy, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Ormsby, Andrew S., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Ornati, Oscar A., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Pagano, Joseph, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Panofsky, Hans, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Paolucci, Daniel J., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Parker, Seymour, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Parsons, Edgar A., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Paton, Roberto Perez, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- P-1 Paterson, John D., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- P-1 Pauk, Walter, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Payne, Bruce, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Perlma, Mark, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- P-1 Perrins, Harlan, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Plant, Nancy Helm, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Poindexter, Webster Ray, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- P-1 Polisar, Eric, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Puchek, Michael, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Radom, Matthew, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Ranck, Kathryn E., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- P-1 -- Reynolds, Judy (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Richardson, J. Henry, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ridgeway, Valentine, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Righter, Bobbyann, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- P-1 -- Rodriguez, Ricardo, 1952-1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Riley, Effey, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- P-1 Ritzer, George, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- P-1 Roman, Paul, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Roseburry, C. R., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- P-1 Roy, Donald F., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ryan, T. A., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sapienzo, Emilio (Dr.), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Sergeant, Edward, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- P-1 Sayin, Afife, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Sayles, Leonard, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Sayre, J. W., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- P-1 Scheepmaker, B., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Schmidhauser, Harold R., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Segal, Martin E., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Sewald, Ralph (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Seppanen, Paavo Antero, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Shackelton, H. E., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Shank, Donald J., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Shaw, I. Bradford, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- P-1 -- Shaw, Malcolm, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- P-1 Shaw, Veronica, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- P-1 Shultz, Andrew, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- P-1 Portus, John, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- P-1 - Schultz, E. B., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- P-1 Siegenthaler, Jurg, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Simon, Robert S., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- P-1 Sirota, David, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Smith, James M. (Dr.), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- P-1 Smith, Patricia, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- P-1 -- Snyder, Allan, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- P-1 Soslow, Neil G., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- P-1 Spinks, Geoffrey, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Spinney, Katherine (Miss), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Stark, Arthur, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- P-1 Stevenson, Doris, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Stever, Marian A., 1951-1961 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- P-1 Stewart, Nathaniel, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Strauss, George, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- P-1 Stucki, Curtis P., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Summers, Clyde W., 1918-1954 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Sutton, Doris, Miss, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Sweetall, Robert V., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Taylor Graham C., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- P-1 Thoren, Theodore, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Thurber, John N., 1946-1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Tropp, Else, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- P-1 Tuna, Prof. Orhan, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- P-1 Uren, Cecilia, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Vlastos, Gregory, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- P-1 Von Eltz, Sylvia, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Vrettos, Louis, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Wagner, Martin, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Walker, Roger, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- P-1 Warriner, Charles K., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- P-1 Wedlake, Raymond C., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- White, Gladys Walker, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Wilkinson Matthews, Ann L., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Willcox, Bertram, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- William, Daniel C., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- P-1 -- Williams, Jane, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Wilson, Robert N., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Windsor, A. L., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Witte, Edwin E., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- P-1 Woods, Ronald H., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Woolf, Anne H., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 23)